Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1950-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage printed materials, 1950-2000; 53.5 linear ft. (107 boxes)
  - In the Process Play - Desert Dwellers (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - In the Process Play - Disability (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Emigres (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Haiti (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Haiti (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Interview with Louis Lantz (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lantz, Louis (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "T. Buttita" (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Interview with Mr. Davidson" (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "Hyperion" (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Forever Child (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Subscription material 1991 - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Before it Hits Home (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Closer Than Ever (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Seagull (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Open House Postcards (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Expect the Unexpected (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Ticket Exchange forms (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - She Stoops to Conquer (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - On the Way Home (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pygmalion (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 40th Anniversary (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Our Town (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - On-Stage at Arena Stage (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - ASA Archives (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - ASA Archives (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Touring Press Clips (USSR and H.K.) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, invitations, etc... (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Development (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Callboard and Alumni Review (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ASA materials (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Season Materials 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Living Stage Materials (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Development Stuff (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Individual Production Flyiers (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Flyers 1957-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Saturday Review, March 27, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - American Theatre (April 1985) and Guide to the Arts (May, 1978) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Washingtonian (Oct. 1970) and Amepnka (1975) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - America's Arena and A Permanent Theatre Home (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Richard Bryan - letters 1982/1983 season archives (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report Working file 1984-1985 season (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Wayne's Cultural Diversity / multiracial casting (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Misc. production brochures (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Misc. brochures (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Brochures (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Brochures (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Programs (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Arena Stage letterhead (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - production showtimes (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Misc. brochures, reports, play bills (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Misc. brochures, playbills, etc. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Misc. brochures (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Misc. brochures (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Brochures, flyers, etc... (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1950 Arena Box Office report (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - General Articals 1970-1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - General Articals 76/77 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - General Articals 77/78 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - General Articals 78/79 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - general articals 80/81 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - general articals 81/82 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - general articals 82/83 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - general articals83/84 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - misc. brochures (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - misc. brochures (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous materials from late 70's to early 80's (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Loose leaf papers.
  - periodicals and journal Articals 1970's - 1980's (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Washington Post advertising (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Handicap materials (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Theatre profiles 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage Associates Listing insert and "The1940's Radio Hour" program (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - tintypes - a ragtime revue (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - group sales/ stationary and teibele ASA listings (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Associates (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Realtor's Subscription Brochure Package 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Mummenschanz stuffer (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 10K "Fund" Run sign up sheet (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Theatre Profiles / 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "In the Process" Programs 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 30th Anniversary Season (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Golden Circel and Student subscription series (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Flyers and Inserts 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Giant Food Associates Night flyer, "A Winter's Tale" (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Arena Stage Associates (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Theatre Profiles 1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Photos (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Misc. flyers and invitations (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - America's Arena and Saturday Review (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - invitation, "Conquest of the South Pole" (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Invitation, "Fences" (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Invitation, "A Doll House" (March 7th) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Invitation, "A Doll House" (March 8th) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Invitation, "Merrily we Roll Along" (Feb. 7th) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Invitation, "Merrily we Roll Along" (Feb. 1st) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Invitation, "Montieth and Rand" (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Invitation, "The man who came to dinner" (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - invitation, "Stand up Tragedy" (Jan. 18th) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Invitation, "Stand up Tragedy" (Jan. 17th) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Letters to subscribers about special performance of "Montieth and Rand" (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Playbill, "Conquest of the South Pole" (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - press release, "Pygmalion" (Feb. 25, 1991) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - press release, "Pygmalion" (Feb. 13, 1991) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Press release, "Born Guilty" and Before it hits Home" (Jan. 25, 1991) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Brochure, "Standup Tragedy" (Jan. 12 - Feb. 18 no year) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - brochure, "On the way Home" June 2 - July 2, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - post card, George Kaufman's 100th birthday celebration, Dec. 10, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - postcard, signature series, March 11, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - postcard, "motieth and Rand" Dec. 12 - Jan. 7th (no year) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - postcard, Signature Series, Feb. 4th 1990 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - postcard, Signature Series, Oct. 29, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - playbill, "Fences", April 20 - July 8, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - brochure, "On the Way Home" 1989-1990 season (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - brochure, Group Sales (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - postcard, "juno and the Paycock" May 4 - June 10 (no year) (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - postcard, "Merrily we Roll Along" Jan. 26 - April 8 (no year) (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - postcard, Season's Greetings discount offer, Dec. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - postcard, "Merrily we Roll Along", Jan. 26 - April 8 (no year) (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - press release, "On the Town" (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - On Stage, Vol. 1 No. 1 (1989 - 1990) (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - On Stage, Vol. 1, No. 2 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - brochure, A Stage Four Workshop, Jan. 22 - 24, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - donation card, George Kaufman 100th Birthday, Nov. 16, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - company letter, Living Stage Theatre (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - 40 year celebration save 20% letter (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - brochure, congressional ticket hotline (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - invitation, "Juno and Paycock" May 9 - 10, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - postcard, seasons greetings 1-% discount (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - postcard, "The Glass Menagerie" (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - postcard, "Fences" (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - postcard, "Merrily we Roll Along" (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - postcard, "A Dolls House" (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - postcard, "A Doll House" March 8th (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - postcard, "Stand-up Tragedy" Jan. 18th (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - postcard, "Conqest of the South Pole" March 21st. (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - postcard, "Stand-up Tragedy", Jan. 17th. (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - postcard, "Fences" (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - postcard, "Merrily we Roll Along" (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - postcard, "Montieth and Rand" (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Coupon, "On the Way Home" (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - invitations, "Fences" (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - invitations, "The Man who can to Dinner" (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - subscription info 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - 40th Anniversary envelopes 1990 - 1991 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - 3 play package holiday special, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Cross Currents, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Seasonal Announcements 1990 - 1991 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - subscription order form (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Coupon promotion (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - five play promotional brochuer (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - subscription forms for the 1989-1990 season (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - emergancy campaign to save the arts brochure (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - 2 show holiday package brochure (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - 3 play package brochure (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - national VIP theatre hotline card (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - 1989-1990 season schedule brochure (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - promotional letter for triple play series (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - "The Proposal" (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - subscription ticket exchange card (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - postcard, "Juno and the Paycock" (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - discount letters to subscribers for "Montieth and Rand" (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - postcard, "Mr. Ibsen Speaks!!!" April 1, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - internship brochure (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - program book/resturant guide 1988-1989 season (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - 1989-1990 season, Sept. - June brochure (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - "a midsummer's night dream", invite/response card (1989-1990) (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - "The Glass Managerie" Invite card 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Signature Series w/Ruby Dee 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Theatre Lover's tour 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - "Glass Managerie" response card/invitation 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - fellows program brochure 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - "On the Way Home" Invitation Response card 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - "Save the Arts" Brochure 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - 3 play holiday special brochure (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - subscription info 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - congressional ticket hotline card 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - 40th anniversary special order form (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - subscription handbook 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - subscription brochure (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - group sales brochure 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - deaf series brochure (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - 1990-1991 anniversary gale information (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - employees only stuffer 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - tele-sec stuffer 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - ushers discount 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - 1989-1990 Season pocket guide (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - "Midsummer's" postcard 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Onstage publication Summer 1991 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Living Stage summer camp (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Living Stage training program (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Living Stage theatre benefit (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - The Creative Projects:Summer 1989 workshops (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Living Stage films program brochure (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - On Stage, Spring 1990 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - 1990-1991 season (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - performance workshops (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - residencies brochure (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Profile (publication) (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - On Stage, Winter 1990 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - On Stage, Winter 1990 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - On Stage, Spring 1991 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Invitation/response card "midsummer's nights dream" (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - postcard, "if you think, it is" (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - postcard, "The Brothers Karamazov" (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - postcard, "of Thee I Sing" (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - postcard, "The Way of the World" (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - postcard, "Of Thee I Sing" (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - flyer: "Love Letters" (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - postcard: "The Skin of our Teeth" (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - program: "Lover Letters" (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - postcard: "Avner the Eccentric" (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - postcard: "A History of African American Theatre" (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - postcard:"Stars and Strips" (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - postcard:"Summer and Smoke", group sales (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - postcard: "Summer and Smoke" (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - invitation: "The Skin of out Teeth", May 12, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - invitation: tea and converstaion with Miss. Manners (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - invitation: "The Way of the World" (Box 13, Folder 131)
  - invitation: "Of Thee I Sing" (Box 13, Folder 132)
  - invitation: "Its the Truth (if you think it is)" (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - invitation: "Its the Truth (if you think it is)" (Box 13, Folder 134)
  - invitation:"The Way of the World" (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - brochure: "The VAT Pass" (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - postcard: "Richard III" (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - postcard: "Blood Knot" (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - invitation: "Summer and Smoke" (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - invitation: "Summer and Smoke" (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - invitation: "The Brothers Karamazov" (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - invitation: "The Brothers Karamazov" (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - invitation: "The Skin of our Teeth" (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - invitation: "Blood knot" (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - playbill: "Avner the Eccentric" (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - subscription handbook 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - orderform: three play package (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - sales prices for 1992-1993 season (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - program advertising rate info 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - printed materials 1992-1993 season (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - program for Fichandler stage dedication (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - invitation: "Antigone in NY" (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - orderform: special 40% off offer (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - invitation: "Of Thee I Sing" (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - "On Stage" Vol. 4, #1 (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - "On Stage" Vol. 4, #2 (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - buttons: "Win with Wintergreen" (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - "On Stage" Vol. 4, #3 (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - reservation card: "Summer and Smoke" (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - cassette: "Merrily We Roll Along" (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - budget - 40th anniv. gala (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - final figures - 40th anniv. gala (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 40th anniv. photo exibit (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 40th Anniv. press kit (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - book (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 40th anniv. council (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 40th anniv. honorary committee (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 40th anniv. White House correspondence (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - letters (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - press letters (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - timetable/deadlines (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 40th anniv. invitation card (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 40th anniv. in-kind donations (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - table sales target (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 40th anniv. guild/dinner committee (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 40th anniv. meeting minutes (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - site arrangements (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 40th anniv. table sales (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 40th anniv. script for presentation (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 40th anniv. gala gifts report (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 40th anniv. regrets acceptances (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 40th anniv. salzo kit (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 40th anniv. gala funds (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - 40th anniv. seating requests (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - 40th anniv. table sales confirmation letters (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - 40th anniv. general information (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - underwriting (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - gala program transcripts (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - reception (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - programs (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - program credits (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - program (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - invitation and program design (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - multi-media program (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - 40th anniv. donated hotel accomadations (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Ads. 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ads. 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Ads. 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Ads. 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Ads. 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - ads. 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ad. in the Daily Rag (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ads. 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - ads. 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - tearsheet files 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - insertion orders (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - playtime (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - ads. 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - ABC ads. 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - tom's picture ads. 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - misc. ads. 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - playtime ads. 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - This Week ads. 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - washington star and post ads. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Star/News (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - ads book 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Washington Star ads. 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Washington Post ads. 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - The Vagabond Players (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - ads. 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - ads. 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - ads 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - ads. 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - ads 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ads. 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - ads. 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - ads 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - ads. 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - ads. 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - ads. 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Israel (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - photos from hippodrome (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - photos from hippodrome (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - photos from hippodrome (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Site map (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - graphics (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Arena Stage history (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Tony Award (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - offical recognitions (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - premieres (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - foreign language articals (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - architecture articals (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - general articals 1950-1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - general articals 1960-1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - general articals 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Misc. playbills/programs (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Living Stage misc. info (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - misc. promotional material 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - misc. promotion 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - misc. promotion 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - misc. promotion 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - misc. promotion 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - misc. promotion 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - misc. promotions, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - misc. promotion 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - misc. promotion 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - misc. promotion 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - misc. promotion 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - misc. promotion 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - misc. promotion 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - misc. promotion 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - misc. promotion 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - misc. promotion 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - misc. promotion 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - misc. promotion 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - misc. promotion 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - invite samples 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - the playwrights carousal of new plays (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 18 promotional cards (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - march 1981 press packet (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage Angels fund raising auction (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - invitations 1984-1985 season (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 30th anniv. promotional material (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - invitations: 1986-1987 season (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - invitations: 1983-1984 season (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - programs: 1982-1983 season (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - opening night invites 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - programs: 1981-1982 season (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - P.P. misc. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - misc. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - 40 years - a great stage of life (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - press releases (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - invitations: 1985-1986 season (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - brochures misc. seasons (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - discount ticket mailings (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - gala opening material (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - events (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - living stage (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - subscriber to ASA (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - 1986 calender (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - annual reports: 1979-1983 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - annual report: 1983-1991 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - America's Arena (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - America's Arena (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - misc. (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - subsrciption envelopes (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - invitation: "Mrs. Klein" (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - invitation: "A Wonderful Life" (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - invitation: "A Wonderful Life" (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - postcard: "A Wonderful Life" (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - reservation card: "The School for Wives" (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - invitation: "Trinidad Sisters" (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - invitation: "The Visit" (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - postcard: "Yerma" (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - subscription letter: 33% off ticket price (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - atfer deadline, subscription renewal letter (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Subscription letter (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - reservation card: "Trinidad Sisters" (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - invitation: "Mrs. Klein" (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - reservation card: "Trinidad Sisters" (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - postcard: "The School for Wives" (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - postcard: "The Time of Your Life" (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - invitations: "The Time of Your Life" (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - invitation: "The Time of You Life" (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - postcard: "Jar the Floor" (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - invitation: "Jar the Floor" (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - invitation: "Jar the Floor" (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - invitation: "The School for Wives" (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - postcard: " Jar the Floor" (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - response cards: "The Time of Your Life" (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - response card: "Jar the Floor" (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - postcard: "The School of Wives" (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - invitation: "The School for Wives" (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - invitation: "The Father" (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - invitation: "The Father" (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - postcard: "The Visit" (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - postcard: "Love or Marriage" (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Congressional Hispanic Caucus special invitation to "Yerma" (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - postcard: "A Wonderful Life" (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - postcard: "On Borrowed Time" (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - info packet on the AT and T presentation of "A Wonderful Life" (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - brochure: Playquest at Arena Stage (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - subscription handbook: 1993-1994 season (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - brochure: 1994-1995 season subscription (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - brochure: "A Community Carol" (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - postcard: "The Skull Beneath the Smile" (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - postcard: "A Community Carol" (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - postcard: "Twelfth Night" (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - postcard: "A Room of One's Own" (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - postcard: "Dancing at Lughnasa" (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - brochure: "The Revengers Comedies" (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - postcard: "The Price" (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - brochure: 4,5 or 6 play packages (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - booklet: "The Revenge of the Comedies" (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - booklet: "A Small World" (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - booklet: "A Room of One's Own" (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - booklet: "A Community Carol" (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - booklet: "The Price" (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - booklet: "Dancing at Lughnasa" (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - invitation: "Twelfth Night" (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - invitation: "A Room of One's Own" (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - invitations: "dancing at lughnasa" (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - invitations: "A Small World" (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - invitation: "A Community Carol" (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - invitation: "A Small World" (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - invitation: "A Community Carol" (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - invitations: "The Price" (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - brochure: student matinee series (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Arena Stage magazine, Sept.-Oct. 1993 (Box 19, Folder 66)